food4rhino.com 2019-05-01

# Privacy | Food4Rhino

**_1.   Introduction_**

Thank you for visiting food4Rhino.  Please read our Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy carefully, as you must agree to both documents to be able to use our Service.

**_2.   Definitions_**

Throughout this document, we may use certain words or phrases, and it is important that you understand what they mean.  The following is a non-exhaustive list of definitions of words and phrases found in this document:

“food4Rhino” refers to our company, known as “McNeel Europe S.L.”; our Site; our Service; or a combination of all or some of the preceding definitions, depending on the context in which the word is used;

“Service” refers to the services that we provide through our Site, including services for developers and our Site itself;

“Site” refers to our website, [www.food4Rhino.com](http://www.food4rhino.com/);

“User” refers to anyone who uses our Service, including general visitors to our Site;

“You” refers to you, the person who is governed by this Privacy Policy.

**_3.   Information Collected_**

_Identifying Information_

We collect certain personal information from you when you sign up to our Service that can be used to identify you, such as your name, alias, e-mail address, app information, and any other information that we deem necessary for the purpose of providing you with our Service or which you provide to us voluntarily. The information we collect from you, to the extent that it is private, is disclosed only in accordance with our Terms of Service and/or this Privacy Policy.

_Non-Identifying Information_

Whenever you visit our Site, we may collect non-identifying information from you, such as your IP address, referring URL, browser, operating system, cookie information, and Internet Service Provider.  Without a subpoena, voluntary compliance on the part of your Internet Service Provider, or additional records from a third party, this information alone cannot usually be used to identify you.

**_4.   Use of Your Information_**

We may use your information to:

  * Enhance or improve User experience, our Site, or our Service.
  * Process transactions.
  * • Transfer to 3rd party developers when you download one of its apps or resources.
  * Send e-mails about our Site or respond to inquiries.
  * Send e-mails and updates about food4Rhino, including our e-mail newsletter.
  * Perform any other function that we believe, in good faith, is necessary to protect the security or proper functioning of our Site or Service.

**_5.   Accessing, Editing, and Removing Your Information_**

In some cases, users may be able to review and edit the personal information they have provided by logging on to the Site and editing their account.  Although most changes may occur immediately, information may still be stored in a web browser’s cache.  We take no responsibility for stored information in your cache, or in other devices that may store information, and disclaim all liability of such.  In addition, from time to time, we may retain residual information about you in our backup and/or database.

**_6.   Cookies_**

This site uses first-party and third-party cookies to provide users with a better experience and service.

First-party cookies are used for three different goals:

  * To maintain the user session if the user is identified to make use of the services provided.
  * To detect functional and technical capabilities of user navigation and, specifically, to detect if JavaScript is enabled.
  * To detect if the user has accepted this terms of use statement relating to cookies.

In the two first cases, cookies are deleted when logging off or closing the browser.  
In the last case, cookies will expire a year after they are created.

Third-party cookies analyze the user experience and collect statistical data anonymously.

These cookies are managed by the Google Analytics service.

This service is managed by Google, which provides services to process statistical data anonymously, and therefore it does not collect personal information.  
This company may use the data to improve their own services, either in their own products or in third-party products.  
You can check all the information concerning this application and its data protection policy at Google Analytics Privacy statement.  
This anonymous information helps us improve our services based on our visitors' experience.

By browsing or using our services, you agree to our use of cookies.

However, at any time, the user can prevent cookies being generated and delete them by selecting the appropriate browser option:

If cookies are deleted, it means that the user does not want to use this website. Any subsequent visit will imply the acceptance of the terms described above.

**_7.   Third Party Websites_**

Food4Rhino or its Users may post links to third party websites on our Site.  These third party websites are not screened for privacy or security issues by food4Rhino, and you release us from any liability for the conduct of these third party websites.

Please be aware that this Privacy Policy, and any other policies in place, in addition to any amendments, does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require disclosure of any personal information relating to members of the Service or Site.  Food4Rhino bears no responsibility for the information collected or used by any advertiser or third party website.  Please review the privacy policy and terms of service for each site you visit through third party links.

**_8.   Third Party Access to Your Information_**

Although you are entering into an Agreement with food4Rhino to disclose your information to us, we do use third party individuals and organizations to assist us, including contractors, web hosts, and others.

Throughout the course of our Service provision we may delegate our authority to collect, access, use, and disseminate your information.  For example, our web host stores the information that you send us, and we may hire outside contractors to perform maintenance or assist us in securing our website.

It is therefore necessary that you grant the third parties we may use in the course of our business the same rights that you afford us under this Privacy Policy.  For this reason, you hereby agree that for every authorization which you grant to us in this Privacy Policy, you also grant it to any third party that we may hire, contract, or otherwise retain the services of for the purpose of operating, maintaining, repairing, or otherwise improving or preserving our website or its underlying files or systems.  You agree not to hold us liable for the actions of any of these third parties, even if we would normally be held vicariously liable for their actions, and that you must take legal action against them directly should they commit any tort or other actionable wrong against you.

Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you authorize us to collect, share, store, and otherwise use your information in conjunction with:

  * Google Analytics

**_9.   Release of Your Information for Legal Purposes_**

At times it may become necessary or desirable for food4Rhino, for legal purposes, to release your information in response to a request from a government agency or a private litigant.  You agree that we may disclose your information to a third party where we believe, in good faith, that it is desirable to do so for the purposes of a civil action, criminal investigation, or other legal matters.  In the event that we receive a subpoena affecting your privacy, we may elect to notify you to give you an opportunity to file a motion to quash the subpoena, or we may attempt to quash it ourselves, but we are not obligated to do either.  We may also proactively report you, and release your information, to third parties when we believe that it is prudent to do so for legal reasons, such as our belief that you have engaged in fraudulent activities.  You release us from any damages that may arise from or relate to the release of your information to a request from law enforcement agencies or private litigants.

**_10.   Commercial and Non-Commercial Communications_**

By providing information to the Site that forms the basis of communications with you, such as contact information, you waive all rights to file complaints concerning unsolicited e-mails from food4Rhino since, by providing such information, you agree to receive communications from us or anyone else covered under this Privacy Policy.  However, you may unsubscribe from certain communications by notifying food4Rhino that you no longer wish to receive solicitations or information and we will endeavor to remove you from the database.

**_11.   Security Measures_**

We take certain measures to enhance the security of our Site and Service, including using SSL certificates and vulnerability scanning.  However, we make no representations as to the security or privacy of your information.  It is in our interest to keep our website secure, but we recommend that you use anti-virus software, firewalls, and other precautions to protect yourself from security threats.

**_12.   Your California Online Privacy Rights_**

Food4Rhino permits residents of California to use its services.  Therefore, it is the intention of food4Rhino to comply with the  _California Business and Professions Code_  §§ 22575-22579.  If you are a California resident, you may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to any third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  Various provisions throughout this Privacy Policy address requirements of the Californian privacy statutes.  In summary, you must presume that we collect electronic information from all visitors.  You may contact us at 4FQ.RYY3Q4@F3GULnPFFO@ with any questions.

**_13.   Your European Privacy Rights_**

Food4Rhino is located within the European Union and follows Directive 95/46/EC of the European Union.  If you have any questions about your privacy or wish to exercise any of your rights under the Directive, please contact us at 4FQ.RYY3Q4@F3GULnPFFO@.

**_14.   International Transfer_**

Your information may be transferred to—and maintained on—computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.  If you are located outside of the Kingdom of Spain and choose to provide information to us, food4Rhino transfers Personal Information to the Kingdom of Spain and processes it there.  Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

**_15.   Amendments_**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.  When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will update this page accordingly and require you to accept the amendments as a condition of your continued use of our Service.

Last Modified:  October 17, 2016
